Cody Dibble

Seattle, WA
(928) 277-3708
hcodydibble@gmail.com
https://linkedin.com/in/codydibble
https://github.com/hcodydibble

Python developer with an understanding of JavaScript and a passion for learning new technologies and concepts. I look forward to advancing technology in the marketplace and growing the product to make an impact.

SKILLS

- Proficient in Python, Django, Pyramid, PostgreSQL, Git, JavaScript, JQuery, Node.JS, HTML5, CSS
- Experience in functional and unit testing in Python and JavaScript
- Excellent communication and teamwork skills

PROJECTS

Cryptomonsters

December 2017 - ec2-34-215-7-234.us-west-2.compute.amazonaws.com

A card collecting app that uses blockchain technology in order for players to get cards. Written using Python and the Django web framework and deployed using AWS.

- Researched cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology.
- Gained knowledge on how to connect together various AWS services including EC2, S3 and RDS.
- Worked in a small team of four using good git workflow.

SpaceRocks

November 2017 - close-encounters.herokuapp.com

A data visualization app for the NASA N.E.O API. Written using Python and the Pyramid web framework and deployed using Heroku.

- Used E.T.L (Extract, Transform, Load) to pull specific data from the API and fill out a PostgrSQL database.
- Learned and used Bokeh to visualize the data pulled from the API.

Report My Wreck

October 2017 - report-my-wreck.herokuapp.com

An app where the user can use google maps to mock up their accident and send it to their insurance agent. Written using JavaScript, JQuery and the Google Maps API and deployed using Heroku.

- Used custom url queries and Google's StaticMaps API to build out map of the user's accident.
- Used jQuery to add usability to the site.

EDUCATION

Code Fellows, Seattle, WA

August 2017 - December 2017

Certificate - Advanced Software Development in Python

- Intensive training in JavaScript, Python, Data Structures
- Pair-programming and small team coding experience

EXPERIENCE

Rudy's Barbershop, Seattle, WA

November 2013 - PRESENT

- Lead a team of 3 co-workers to keep shop running at high efficiency
- Make and manage appointments
- Maintain the look and feel of the shop

Dawn of the Donut, Spokane, WA

March 2013 - August 2013

- Prepare and bake donuts
- Decorate donuts
- Deliver finished donuts to various shops